directoryofgames.com 2016-06-27

# Directory of Games - The greatest MMORPG games online

_Last modified on July 14, 2011_

Directory of Games respects your privacy and strives to offer you the best service possible with the most security available to us. Directory of Games requests and uses certain information provided by you to allow a more personalized experience while browsing the site. Below you will find our privacy policy, which outlines the types of information we collect and how it�s used on the site.

**Changes of the Privacy Policy**

Occasionally, Directory of Games will update this privacy policy. If this document is updated, an announcement will be posted to ensure that all current and potential members accessing the site are made aware that the privacy policy has undergone a change. It is your responsibility to make sure you read the privacy policy if and when it is updated. In the instance that you miss the announcement, you may check the "Last modified date" located above.

**Advertising**

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/).

**Information Collected**

In order to experience the Directory of Games.com website in a more personalized manner, we ask that you supply us with your first and last name, the country you are from, and a valid email address. This information is primarily used for personalizing your experience on the Directory of Games.com website, and in some circumstances, it is also used to verify that the account is your account in the instance you lose your login details. This information is not, and never will be distributed to any third parties without your approval unless it is required under certain circumstances as listed below:

      **i.** Directory of Games will disclose your personal information if required to do so in order to assist in actions involving the law or to assist in the legal process in issues involving the Directory of Games.com website.  
      **ii** Directory of Games will disclose your personal information if it is required to protect and defend the rights of property for the Directory of Games.com website, or to protect the safety of the members of the Directory of Games.com website community.

**Maintaining Your Personal Information**

Any information submitted to Directory of Games is stored in a secure database that is only accessible by the owner of the website and trusted members of the Director of Games website. This information is only accessed in the events listed above, or to verify the owner of an account. The information stored is not disclosed or sold to people or companies outside of the Directory of Games website.

Your personal information is also protected by the password and email address you chose when you signed up. To aide in the prevention of this information getting into the wrong hands, we advise that you do not share your email and password with anyone. Staff on the Directory of Games.com website will never ask for your password or email address as they do not need it.

**Use of Cookies**

Directory of Games requires users to use cookies in order to browse the site. These cookies that are stored on your computer store the information required to offer you a more personalized experience. If you do not wish to allow the use of cookies, you will still be able to view most areas of the site, but you will be limited in the areas you may view and your visit will not be a personalized experience.

If you have any questions or concerns regarding this privacy policy, please email [admin@directoryofgames.com](mailto:admin@directoryofgames.com).
